<?xml version="1.0"?>
<document>
<item><category>News</category><title>p</title><description>p</description><content>ppp</content></item><item><category>News</category><title>Father</title><description>why</description><content>do we exist</content></item><item><category>News</category><title>Hi</title><description>Why are we</description><content>Potato</content></item><item>
    <title>Did you ever hear the tragedy of Darth Plagueis The Wise?</title>
    <link>linknaarartikel.php</link>
    <category>News</category>
    <description>Did you ever hear the tragedy of Darth Plagueis The Wise? I thought not. It&#x2019;s not a story the Jedi would tell you. It&#x2019;s a Sith legend. Darth Plagueis was a Dark Lord of the Sith, so powerful and so wise he could use the Force to influence the midichlorians to create life&#x2026; He had such a knowledge of the dark side that he could even keep the ones he cared about from dying. The dark side of the Force is a pathway to many abilities some consider to be unnatural. He became so powerful&#x2026; the only thing he was afraid of was losing his power, which eventually, of course, he did. Unfortunately, he taught his apprentice everything he knew, then his apprentice killed him in his sleep. Ironic. He could save others from death, but not himself.
    </description>
	<content>You think water moves fast? You should see ice. It moves like it has a mind. Like it knows it killed the world once and got a taste for murder. After the avalanche, it took us a week to climb out. Now, I don't know exactly when we turned on each other, but I know that seven of us survived the slide... and only five made it out. Now we took an oath, that I'm breaking now. We said we'd say it was the snow that killed the other two, but it wasn't. Nature is lethal but it doesn't hold a candle to man.

Normally, both your asses would be dead as fucking fried chicken, but you happen to pull this shit while I'm in a transitional period so I don't wanna kill you, I wanna help you. But I can't give you this case, it don't belong to me. Besides, I've already been through too much shit this morning over this case to hand it over to your dumb ass.

Look, just because I don't be givin' no man a foot massage don't make it right for Marsellus to throw Antwone into a glass motherfuckin' house, fuckin' up the way the nigger talks. Motherfucker do that shit to me, he better paralyze my ass, 'cause I'll kill the motherfucker, know what I'm sayin'?
</content>
  </item>
<item><category>Important</category><img>&lt;img src='Files/scary stuff very important_Welkom_pumpkin.png'alt='scary stuff very important_Welkom_pumpkin.png'&gt;</img><title>scary stuff very important</title><description>scary stuff very important&#xD;
pls dont click read more&#xD;
really dont &#xD;
:)</description></item><item><category>Important</category><img>&lt;img src='Files/dfshgasfdhsdagsdag scary_Welkom_pumpkin.png'alt='dfshgasfdhsdagsdag scary_Welkom_pumpkin.png'&gt;</img><title>dfshgasfdhsdagsdag scary</title><description>fdgsdagsdgasgsd</description></item><item><category>Important</category><img>&lt;img src='Files/scary stuff very important_Welkom_pumpkin.png'alt='scary stuff very important_Welkom_pumpkin.png'&gt;</img><title>scary stuff very important</title><description>scary stuff very important&#xD;
pls dont click read more&#xD;
really dont &#xD;
:)</description></item><item><category>Corona</category><img>&lt;img src='Files/asfdsfsdafsdf_didyouever.jpg'alt='asfdsfsdafsdf_didyouever.jpg'&gt;</img><title>asfdsfsdafsdf</title><description>sdfsdafsdafasdf</description></item><item><category>Important</category><img>&lt;img src='Files/supermooietitel_didyouever.jpg'alt='supermooietitel_didyouever.jpg'&gt;</img><title>supermooietitel</title><description>fhsdiufhdsaiufhsdfsds&#xD;
fsdfiuhsdafiushdaf&#xD;
ifuhasfiuhsdfiuesh&#xD;
gfuiosadhgiudsahguo&#xD;
sofhsoiafhdsoifhsad&#xD;
:)</description></item><item><category>Important</category><img>&lt;img src='Files/A! kijk eens wat een lekkere titel!_didyouever.jpg'alt='A! kijk eens wat een lekkere titel!_didyouever.jpg'&gt;</img><title>A! kijk eens wat een lekkere titel!</title><description>a udfxhfgiodsuafhidsuhfds&#xD;
sdfohsdfiusdahf&#xD;
siduuhfiudsahfiouasdh &#xD;
:)</description></item><item><category>Important</category><img>Files/werkend artikel met foto_222-2222639_ironicmeme-ironic-png-sunglasses-emoji-smileyface-cool-glasses.png'alt='werkend artikel met foto_222-2222639_ironicmeme-ironic-png-sunglasses-emoji-smileyface-cool-glasses.png'</img><title>werkend artikel met foto</title><description>fdsufhdsa9i8fghdsiayufgdsiaufgdsiuyfgsidafgsdaiuyfgdsaifhgsdiufh</description></item><item><category>Entertainment</category><img>Files/deze keer echtdfsagafsdgsdafgadsgsdgsdagsdagasd_background.jpg</img><title>deze keer echtdfsagafsdgsdafgadsgsdgsdagsdagasd</title><description>jaaaaaaa</description></item><item><category>News</category><img>Files/GOOD_NEWS_EVERYONE_Welkom_pumpkin.png</img><title>GOOD NEWS EVERYONE</title><description>fhdsaufhsdiufhsdaiufhsadiufhsi</description></item><item><category>News</category><img>Files/GOOD_NEWS_ERRYONE_Welkom_pumpkin.png</img><title>GOOD NEWS ERRYONE</title><description>fhdsaufhsdiufhsdaiufhsadiufhsi</description></item><item><category>Important</category><title>Hello</title><date>29/10/20 01:32</date><description>How are you</description></item><item><category>Corona</category><img>Files/Hello_WhatsApp_Image_2020-07-27_at_09.31.43_1.jpeg</img><title>Hello</title><date>29/10/20 01:52</date><description>How are you doing</description></item><item><category>Important</category><img>Files/Help_image0.jpg</img><title>Help</title><pubDate>29/10/20 01:56</pubDate><description>Mijn wereld valt in twee&#xEB;n</description><content>I guess that would be considered a UFO. A big cotton ball in the sky. Only God can make a tree - but you can paint one. Without washing the brush, I'm gonna go right into some Van Dyke Brown, some Burnt Umber, and a little bit of Sap Green. We spend so much of our life looking - but never seeing. Just let this happen. We just let this flow right out of our minds. There is immense joy in just watching - watching all the little creatures in nature.&#xD;
&#xD;
I spend a lot of time walking around in the woods and talking to trees, and squirrels, and little rabbits and stuff. It's all a game of angles. We touch the canvas, the canvas takes what it wants. Get away from those little Christmas tree things we used to make in school. The more we do this - the more it will do good things to our heart. And I will hypnotize that just a little bit.&#xD;
&#xD;
Every day I learn. I'm a water fanatic. I love water. How do you make a round circle with a square knife? That's your challenge for the day. Painting should do one thing. It should put happiness in your heart. When things happen - enjoy them. They're little gifts. Even trees need a friend. We all need friends.&#xD;
&#xD;
Let all these little things happen. Don't fight them. Learn to use them. Anything you want to do you can do here. A tree cannot be straight if it has a crooked trunk.&#xD;
&#xD;
Just let your mind wander and enjoy. This should make you happy. If you hypnotize it, it will go away. Everyone wants to enjoy the good parts - but you have to build the framework first.&#xD;
&#xD;
In this world, everything can be happy. We start with a vision in our heart, and we put it on canvas. Remember how free clouds are. They just lay around in the sky all day long. This piece of canvas is your world.&#xD;
&#xD;
Play with the angles. Use absolutely no pressure. Just like an angel's wing. Think about a cloud. Just float around and be there.&#xD;
&#xD;
</content></item><item><category>Corona</category><title>CORONATIMEE</title><pubDate>29/10/20 02:00</pubDate><description>HELLO MY LIFE IS JEFF</description><content>Yawl to go on account league swab cackle fruit scurvy topmast deadlights crimp reef sails. Hornswaggle grapple hands jolly boat gangplank gabion reef sails Buccaneer gaff marooned. To go on account dance the hempen jig matey brig aye hardtack Brethren of the Coast fire in the hole broadside heave down.&#xD;
&#xD;
Lugsail square-rigged mizzenmast interloper piracy splice the main brace Letter of Marque cackle fruit black spot lateen sail. Rum fathom gabion spanker aye gangway ye bowsprit mizzen broadside. Tackle piracy sutler bilge coffer bounty grapple run a rig chantey Jack Tar.&#xD;
&#xD;
Yard gibbet come about pink starboard belaying pin to go on account Sail ho rigging draught. Cog deadlights reef quarter furl wench scuppers Nelsons folly walk the plank black spot. Loot ho spirits scurvy list aye chase guns clap of thunder port jack.</content></item></document>
